Heather Holman

Pharmacist with MBA

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Heather-Holman/2269e051fc597368

I am interested in an opportunity to work as a pharmacist in an organization that encourages innovation and allows me to utilize my previous experiences and academic knowledge of pharmacy.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Consultant Pharmacist

MedKare Pharmacy - Kansas City, MO - 2011 to 2015

Responsibilities

Responsibilities include: Provide drug regimen reviews and disease assessment/management at facilities and make recommendations to other healthcare professionals, input/evaluate/clarify/document/dispense prescriptions for long term care facilities, facilitate communication with other healthcare professionals, ensure timely medication order processing and drug distribution from the order arriving at the pharmacy until delivery to the facility, customer service, conflict resolution, manage and coordinate the activities of pharmacy technicians and delivery drivers, ensure medications are ordered and maintain appropriate inventory controls within the pharmacy, on call responsibilities, managing pharmacy workflow and efficiency

Pharmacy Intern

CVS Pharmacy - Kansas City, MO - 2007 to 2011

Responsibilities include: input and filling of prescriptions, assist in managing pharmacy work flow and efficiency, facilitate

communication with other health care professionals, dosage calculations, customer service, and assist with conflict resolution

Mental Health Technician

Barnes-Jewish Hospital - St. Louis, MO - 2002 to 2007

Responsibilities include: working on Geriatric Psychiatry Unit, Acute Psychiatry

Unit and Adult Psychiatry Unit, administer the MMSE and other testing, take and document vital signs, test and document blood sugar, obtain EKGs, attain labs, facilitate

group discussion for clients, evaluate client's status based on their care plan, assist clients with ADLs, and ensure client safety

Server, Hostess, Bartender

Longhorn Steakhouse - St. Louis, MO - 1999 to 2006

Responsibilities include: customer service, perform conflict resolution, facilitate long term customer relationships, manage other servers workload, and complete section assignments

EDUCATION

Master's of Business Administration in Entrepreneurship and Management of Information System

University of Missouri-Kansas City - Kansas City, MO

2007 to 2013

Doctor of Pharmacy

University of Missouri - Kansas City, MO January 2006 to January 2011

Bachelor of Art in Psychology

Fontbonne University - St. Louis, MO 1999 to 2003

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration

Fontbonne University 1999 to 2003

SKILLS

QS1, Access, Excel, Word

CERTIFICATIONS

Pharmacist by Missouri state board of pharmacy

2011 to October 2016

Pharmacist by Kansas state board of pharmacy

2011 to June 2017

Pharmacist by Pennsylvania state board of pharmacy (in progress)

National certified in Pharmacy-Based Immunization Delivery